allguitartabs.com 2004-12-06

# All Guitar Tabs - Privacy Statement

**Legal Issues...**

This webpage and all materials on this server (unless stated otherwise) are Copyright of AllGuitarTabs.com . It is prohibited by law to copy/re-make these pages without written permission from the author. You may not link to any files on these servers without written permission from the author. Any individual found to be breaking these rules will have their web hosts and ISPs contacted without warning.

**Privacy Statement...**

During the process of delivering our service to you, AllGuitarTabs.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number. However, AllGuitarTabs.com does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by AllGuitarTabs.com is used for the purpose of demographics. In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific ad (this ad may ask you to fill out a survey or provide your zip code). If this does occur, AllGuitarTabs.com may collect this information on behalf of an advertiser. This information is used by an advertiser to respond to your request. In addition, AllGuitarTabs.com may combine this information with other users' information and review it in an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who view a specific type of ad or visit a particular kind of website.
